<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Workflow Hacks on Engineering @ Logic Soft</title>
    <link>https://devblog.logicsoft.co.in/tags/workflow-hacks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Workflow Hacks on Engineering @ Logic Soft</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Logic Soft Pvt. Ltd.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2021 21:34:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://devblog.logicsoft.co.in/tags/workflow-hacks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Quick access with SystemTrayMenu</title>
      <link>https://devblog.logicsoft.co.in/posts/quick-access-everything-with-systemtraymenu/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2021 21:34:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devblog.logicsoft.co.in/posts/quick-access-everything-with-systemtraymenu/</guid>
      <description>Problem Being head of engineering at a firm means having to juggle a lot of context. And in this quest, I am always looking for ways to optimize my workflow. I can (greatly) simplify all of the work I do into these categories:
 Talking to folks &amp;ndash; Zoom  Usually via pre defined links - My personal link / Standup link / My founder&amp;rsquo;s personal link   My own work &amp;ndash; Visual Studio  Open a project in Visual Studio from my local directory of projects   Collaboration &amp;ndash; GitHub  Open a project in GitHub to log an issue / review a pull request    A tool that I already use quite extensively is Key Pirinha which is the Alfred/Spotlight/Launchy equivalent for windows and is blazing fast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>scrcpy with autoadb</title>
      <link>https://devblog.logicsoft.co.in/posts/scrcpy-with-autoadb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 08:59:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devblog.logicsoft.co.in/posts/scrcpy-with-autoadb/</guid>
      <description>This post is mirrored with permission from Parthasarathy&amp;rsquo;s blog
Control android device over adb Required tools ADB
Android Debug Bridge (adb) is a versatile command-line tool that lets you communicate with a device. The adb command facilitates a variety of device actions, such as installing and debugging apps, and it provides access to a Unix shell that you can use to run a variety of commands on a device.
scrcpy</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
